Are you infected?
One Point O is a drama, horror, mystery film directed by Jeff Renfroe.
Paranoid computer programmer Simon wakes up to
find a package in his room one day.
Despite attempts at securing his apartment, the packages keep arriving.
While cameras watch Simon's every move, he struggles to find the
answers to the mysterious forces taking over his life.
Simon, played by Jeremy Sisto.
Derrick, played by Udo Kier.
Trish, played by Deborah Kara Unger.
Howard, played by Lance Henriksen.
Neighbour, played by Bruce Payne.
Hiep Pham, played by Richard Rees.
Paranoia: 1.0 (originally One Point O, also known as 1.0, One Point Zero, Version 1.0, and Virus 1.0) is a 2004
cyberpunk dystopian horror mystery written and directed by Jeff Renfroe and Marteinn Thorsson.
The film stars Jeremy Sisto and Deborah Unger and features Lance
Henriksen, Eugene Byrd, Bruce Payne and Udo Kier.
The film explores themes of mind control, computer,
paranoia, dystopia, nanotechnology.
The tone is dark and emotional and thought_provoking.